// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which temple dedicated to the sun-god is shaped like a chariot?",
    answer: "Sun Temple, Konark",
    options: [
      "Sun Temple, Konark",
      "Lotus Temple, New Delhi",
      "Surya Pahar Temple, Assam",
      "Jagannath Temple, Puri"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which national park harbours the largest number of one-horned Rhinos?",
    answer: "Kaziranga National Park",
    options: [
      "Periyar National Park",
      "Corbett National Park",
      "Kaziranga National Park",
      "Kanha National Park"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which monument was built by the Mughal emperor Akbar?",
    answer: "Fatehpur Sikhri",
    options: [
      "Qutub Minar",
      "Red Fort",
      "Charminar",
      "Fatehpur Sikhri"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is Jantar Mantar?",
    answer: "An Astronomical Observatory",
    options: [
      "A Fort",
      "An Astronomical Observatory",
      "A Mughal Garden",
      "A Museum"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Where did Buddha attain enlightenment?",
    answer: "Bodhgaya",
    options: [
      "Bodhgaya",
      "Lumbini",
      "Sarnath",
      "Kushinagar"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Where is Akbar's Tomb located in India?",
    answer: "Arga",
    options: [
      "Ghaziabad",
      "Arga",
      "Noida",
      "Allahabad"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Where is Golconda Fort located in India?",
    answer: "Telangana",
    options: [
      "Telangana",
      "Delhi",
      "Punjab",
      "Rajastan"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which famous monument was built by Mohammed Quli Qutab Shah in 1951 to commemorate the end of Plague?",
    answer: "Charminar",
    options: [
      "Jama Masjid",
      "Mecca Masjid",
      "Charminar",
      "Toli Masjid"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Where is Sun Temple located?",
    answer: "Konark",
    options: [
      "Sambalpur",
      "Rourkela",
      "Belgam",
      "Konark"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Where is Elephanta Caves located?",
    answer: "Mumbai",
    options: [
      "Madurai",
      "Bhopal",
      "Mumbai",
      "Vizag"
    ]
  },

  
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];